export const navLinks = [
   {
     id: "/",
     title: "home",
   },
   {
     id: "/login",
     title: "quizzes",
   },
   {
     id: "/about",
     title: "about",
   },
   {
      id: "/contact",
      title: "contact us",
    },
 ];

export const secureLinks = [
   {
     id: "/quizzes",
     title: "quizzes",
   },
   {
     id: "/about",
     title: "about",
   },
   {
      id: "/contact",
      title: "contact us",
    },
  {
     id: "/logout",
     title: "logout",
   },
 ];

export const questionTest =[{'question': 'What is the derivative of x^2?', 'correctanswer': '2x', 'wrongoption1': 'x^2', 'wrongoption2': '2', 'wrongoption2': 'x'}, 
{'question': 'What is the integral of x^3?', 'correctanswer': '1/4x^4 + C', 'wrongoption1': '1/3x^3 + C', 'wrongoption2': '1/2x^2 + C', 'wrongoption3':'1/5x^5 + C'}, 
{'question':'What is the derivative of sin(x)?','correctanswer':'cos(x)','wrongoption1':'sin(x)','wrongoption2':'tan(x)','wrongoption2':'sec(x)'}, 
{'question':'What is the integral of cos(x)?','correctanswer':'-sin(x)+C','wrongoption1':'-cos(x)+C','wrongoption2':'-tan(x)+C','wrongoption3':'-sec(x)+C'}, 
{'question':'What is the derivative of e^(-ax)?','correctanswer':'-a*e^(-ax)','wrongoption1':'-e^(-ax)','wrongoption2':'-a*e^ax','wrongoption3':'-e^ax'}, 
{'question':"What is the integral of 1/(1+ x²)", "correctanswer": "arctan ( x ) + C", "wrongoption": "arcsin ( x ) + C", " wrong option": "arccos ( x ) + C", " wrong option": "ln ( 1+ x² ) + C"}, 
{'question': 'What is the derivative of ln ( x ) ?', 'correctanswer': '1/ x ', 'wrongoption': 'ln ( x ) ', 'wrongoption': 'ln ( 1/ x ) ', 'wrongoption': '1/ ln ( x ) '}, 
{'question': 'What is the integral of 1 / √ ( 1 - x² ) ?', 'correctanswer': 'arcsin ( x ) + C', 'wrongoption': 'arctan ( x ) + C', 'wrongoption': 'arccos ( x ) + C',"wrongoption": 'ln ( 1 - √ ( 1 - x² )) + C'},
{'question': 'What is the derivative of cosh⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡⁡( ax )', 'correctanswer' : 'a * sinh ⁡ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ ⁢ a * cosh' ,'wrongoption' : 'a * cosh' ,'wrongoption' : 'sinh' ,'wrongoption' : 'cosh' }, 
 { 'question' : 'What is the integral of sec 2 ax' , 'correctanswer' : 'tan ax + C' ,'wrongoption' : 'sec ax + C' ,'wrongoption' : 'cot ax + C' ,'wrongoption' : 'csc ax + C '}, 
 { 'question' : 'What is the derivative of tanh ax' , 'correctanswer' : 'a * sech 2 ax' ,'wrongoption' : 'a * tanh ax' ,'wrongoption' : 'sech 2 ax' ,'wrongoption' : 'sech ax' }, 
 { 'question' : 'What is the integral of e − ax cos bx dx' , 'correctanswer' : 'e − ax sin bx b − a / b 2 − a 2 +C' ,'wrongoption' : 'e − ax cos bx b − a / b 2 − a 2+C' ,'wrongoptions':'in bxe−axb−a/b2−a2+C', 'wrongoption' : 'Cos Bxe−AxB−A/B2−A2+C' }];

export const about =[
  "Welcome to our company, where we have developed an innovative app that helps students study smarter, not harder. Our app uses AI technology to analyze the study materials you provide and create customized quizzes for you to practice and prepare for your exams.",
  "At our company, we understand the challenges students face when it comes to test preparation. With so much material to cover and limited time to study, it can be overwhelming to know where to begin. Our app simplifies the process by allowing you to simply paste your study materials into the app, and it does the rest. ",
  "Our AI technology scans your material and creates a series of quizzes that are tailored to your specific needs. The quizzes cover the most important information, so you can focus on what matters most for your exam. Plus, the app adapts to your learning style and adjusts the difficulty level of the questions as you progress.",
  "We believe that learning should be engaging and fun, which is why we designed our app to be user-friendly and interactive. You can track your progress and see how you are improving over time, which can help boost your confidence and motivation.",
  "Whether you are studying for a big exam, or just want to reinforce your knowledge on a particular subject, our app is the perfect tool for you. We are dedicated to helping students achieve their academic goals, and we are committed to providing a high-quality and reliable product.",
  "Thank you for choosing our app as your study companion. We are confident that it will help you succeed in your academic pursuits."]